And Assalam Walekum, in this video I have
brought three more great opportunities for you,
one of them is Sperm and
Work from Home, you have to work from home
if you get selected here
then the company will provide you laptop here
internet connection the name of the company
is Sutherland, we will discuss and do
boond job opening watch the full video, we will
discuss a lot of job skins at once,
before that if you are on my channel
then please subscribe and press the bell icon so
that you do
not miss any update, I will
discuss a portion here liking and sharing,
that moment work from home role will be
storage technical support sequence
pure dealership here your experience should be
between one year to six years
regular more than seven lakh salt
Hyderabad Pune Chennai Delhi NCR Mumbai
and
subscribe here
eyes advantage here the
link to apply is in the description box latest
notification if you
subscribe
on the channel
question here you are watching this is
festive  Talking about qualification, if you have
passed 12th here, both can apply here,
okay, there is no job in this field
here, you have to do insurance
sales, don't call me, okay, please do it here and the
shift will be of 10 hours,
contact number for applying here and
in the description box of the email, if you are
interested in doing the job, subscribe here to get appointed for you,
if you have the
advantage here, you
can apply by going to the description box, in this video we
subscribe,
comment,
like, share it with your friends,
you can support me by
subscribing to my channel, R Life